[
    {
        "question": "Which landmark is located in India?",
        "answers": ["Eiffel Tower", "Taj Mahal", "Great Wall of China", "Statue of Liberty"],
        "correctAnswer": "Taj Mahal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the ancient wonder located in Egypt?",
        "answers": ["Colosseum", "Great Pyramid of Giza", "Stonehenge", "Machu Picchu"],
        "correctAnswer": "Great Pyramid of Giza"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which landmark is in Paris?",
        "answers": ["Big Ben", "Eiffel Tower", "Leaning Tower of Pisa", "Sydney Opera House"],
        "correctAnswer": "Eiffel Tower"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the famous clock tower in London?",
        "answers": ["Big Ben", "Leaning Tower of Pisa", "Statue of Liberty", "Eiffel Tower"],
        "correctAnswer": "Big Ben"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which landmark is located in the United States?",
        "answers": ["Machu Picchu", "Statue of Liberty", "Great Wall of China", "Taj Mahal"],
        "correctAnswer": "Statue of Liberty"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the ancient city in Peru?",
        "answers": ["Machu Picchu", "Petra", "Colosseum", "Stonehenge"],
        "correctAnswer": "Machu Picchu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which landmark is located in Rome?",
        "answers": ["Colosseum", "Eiffel Tower", "Big Ben", "Taj Mahal"],
        "correctAnswer": "Colosseum"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the famous leaning tower in Italy?",
        "answers": ["Leaning Tower of Pisa", "Eiffel Tower", "Big Ben", "Statue of Liberty"],
        "correctAnswer": "Leaning Tower of Pisa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which landmark is located in Australia?",
        "answers": ["Sydney Opera House", "Eiffel Tower", "Big Ben", "Statue of Liberty"],
        "correctAnswer": "Sydney Opera House"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the ancient stone circle in England?",
        "answers": ["Stonehenge", "Colosseum", "Machu Picchu", "Petra"],
        "correctAnswer": "Stonehenge"
    }
]